bloggertreff.com 2018-02-05

# PRIVACY POLICY – Blogger Treff

Introduction

This privacy policy (“Policy”) and this site’s Terms of Service (together the “Terms”) govern all use of http://bloggertreff.com and that site’s services (together the “Site” or “Services”). The owners and contributors to the Site will be referred to as “we,” “us,” or “our” in this Policy. By using the Site or its Services, and/or by clicking anywhere on this Site to agree to the Terms and this Policy, you are deemed to be a “user” for purposes of this Policy. You and every other user (“you” or “User” as applicable) are subject to this Policy. You and each user also agree to the Terms by using the Services. In these Terms, the word “Site” includes the site referenced above, its owner(s), contributors, suppliers, licencors, and other related parties.

We provide this privacy statement explaining our online information practices, so that you can decide whether and how to interact with the Site and the Services.

We may release your information when we deem it appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Please also review our Terms of Use section that governs the use and the users of the Site.

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. If we have your email address, we may also send an email notifying you of any changes.

Mobile Device Privacy

The following applies to our site, when viewed on a mobile device:  
When accessed with a mobile device, our site may collect information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you have, device identifiers, and information about your use of the site. Regardless of the device you use to access the site, it will also collect information you provide, as well as information about your interaction with the site and its content.

If location services are activated on your mobile device, our site may collect information about the location of your device. Your mobile network service providers may collect device-specific information, such as a device identifier, when you use our website or one of our mobile applications. This information collected by your mobile network service will not be associated with your user account with us, or with your personally identifiable information.

We use Google as an advertising services provider for the Site. Users may opt out of Google’s use of the DART use-tracking cookie by visiting the Google advertising Policies & Principles page. If you opt out of ad tailoring, you will still see ads, but they will not be based on your browsing history, and they may appear in other languages.

Disputes

We are based in and you are contracting to use our Site. This Policy and all matters arising from your use of the Site are governed by and will be construed according to the laws of , without regard to any choice of laws rules of any jurisdiction. The federal courts and state courts that have geographical jurisdiction over disputes arising at our office location in will be the only permissible venues for any and all disputes arising out of or in connection with this Policy or the Site and Service.

No Users Under the Age of 13

The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 should not use the Site at any time. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected information from anyone under the age of 13, we will erase that information from our servers. It is a violation of our Terms of Service for children under the age of 13 to use the Site.

Terms Contact

If you have any questions about these Terms, please address them to alikhanjatoi8@gmail.com.

Last Updated

These terms were last updated on January 23, 2018
